<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">my people</string>

    <string name="nombre_pueblo">CHINACOTA</string>
    <string name="bt_hoteles">HOTELS</string>
    <string name="bt_restaurantes">RESTAURANTS</string>
    <string name="bt_sitios">TOURIST SITES</string>

    <string name="descripcionHoteles">
        In Chinacota you will find nice hotels and parks for each of the
        members of your family and friends.

        Being such a tourist place you will have a lodging with an excellent service and availability for
        provide you with the best comfort and enjoy your vacation with a lodging made for
        you.
    </string>

    <string name="descripcionRestaurantes">
        In Chinacota you will find new experiences with your palate because you have
        to encourage you to try the gastronomic diversity of this beautiful place.

        Some of its gastronomic delights are:
        * Cacaitos chitareros: This is a sweet derived from panela that together with
        other ingredients form one of the sweets most consumed by the population
        local.
    </string>

    <string name="descripcionSitios">
        Welcome to chinacota, a very welcoming town for you and your family,
        full of many places to know enjoy its climate in the part of
        head of the town known as iscala, there pordar generated a campsite with your
        friends and enjoy its green mountains.
    </string>

    <string name="opcion1">Spanihs</string>
    <string name="opcion2">English</string>
    <string name="opcion3">Italian</string>
    <string name="opcion4">About us</string>

    <!-- Textos de la parte de acerca de:  -->
    <string name="camponombredev">Developer: Juan David Gafaro Garcia</string>
    <string name="descripcion_dev">Nice to meet you it was a pleasure to carry out the development
    of this great android project.
    It was proposed to develop an app that was focused on publicizing some of the surrounding towns
    revealing its most striking parts for future tourists; Well, with that you will have a context
    clearer about the place which is going to be visited, obtaining key data to enjoy this moment
    in the best way.</string>
    <string name="set_contacto">If you are interested in hiring my services you can do it through:
    Mail: davidGG123@gmail.com
    cell phone: 3225297564
    </string>





</resources>